[Music] (41%); [Speech] (80%)
⚡ Fall Down
⚡ Punching
[Music] (26%); [Speech] (80%)
[Smash, crash] (20%)
⚡ Fall Down
[Smash, crash] (33%)
[Music] (89%); [Speech] (74%)
[Music] (50%); [Speech] (67%)
[Music] (26%); [Speech] (85%)
⚡ Punching
⚡ Fall Down
[Speech] (94%)
⚡ Punching
👁 helicopter (mixing bowl)
[Gunshot, gunfire] (20%)
[Fusillade] (20%)
[Explosion] (26%); [Gunshot, gunfire] (20%); ⚡ Fall Down
[Speech] (98%)
👁 dog (American black bear, black bear, Ursus americanus, Euarctos americanus); 👁 cat (American black bear, black bear, Ursus americanus, Euarctos americanus)
[Music] (50%)
[Speech] (26%)
[Music] (41%)
[Explosion] (20%); [Gunshot, gunfire] (26%)
[Vehicle] (20%); 👁 helicopter (modem)
[Speech] (97%)
👁 helicopter (modem)
⚡ Punching
[Walk, footsteps] (33%)
[Speech] (74%)
[Roar] (26%); [Roaring cats (lions, tigers)] (26%)
[Car] (26%); [Motor vehicle (road)] (26%); [Vehicle] (41%)
[Vehicle] (33%)
[Music] (20%)
[Vehicle] (20%)
[Thump, thud] (26%)
[Explosion] (26%); [Gunshot, gunfire] (26%)
[Explosion] (50%); [Gunshot, gunfire] (67%)
[Arrow] (41%); [Thump, thud] (50%)
[Breaking] (33%); [Glass] (33%); ⚡ Fall Down
[Thump, thud] (20%)
[Explosion] (20%); [Gunshot, gunfire] (33%)
⚡ Punching
[Rail transport] (26%); [Railroad car, train wagon] (20%); [Train] (26%); [Vehicle] (50%)
[Music] (100%)
[Smash, crash] (41%); [Whack, thwack] (20%)
[Music] (94%)
[Music] (98%)
👁 dog (Appenzeller)
⚡ Fall Down
⚡ Punching
[Smash, crash] (33%); [Whack, thwack] (20%)
[Music] (67%)
[Smash, crash] (20%)
[Music] (20%)
[Music] (80%)
⚡ Punching
[Music] (94%)
[Speech] (26%)
[Music] (59%)
[Aircraft] (41%); [Helicopter] (41%); [Vehicle] (59%)
[Speech] (89%)
[Music] (33%)
⚡ Fall Down
[Speech] (89%)
⚡ Punching
[Music] (26%); [Speech] (80%)
[Speech] (41%)
[Music] (20%)
[Music] (33%)
[Speech] (89%)
[Silence] (80%)